this is where my empathy comes in.
Where it doesn't is, you know,
when you have a room full of people that do agree with you,
we have this opportunity to come together.
And you're kind of mocking people when they do.
So you mocked Sarah a little bit
when you guys clearly had a common interest
and goal to reach.
So I can tell you're agitated.
I wanna bring that all down, please.
I'm guessing you're not going to, but let's see.
No, no, I'm going to.
I do wanna point out some contradictions.
First and foremost, I don't believe you're pro-American
in the value system that you claim to uphold,
especially with free speech,
if you're not willing to debate people
that don't share your values.
That's very un-American.
Do you believe Donald Trump's plan
for Gaza is ethnic cleansing?
I don't believe it's ethnic cleansing,
but I, because it's not his plan.
It is his plan.
He said it's my plan.
No, he's obeying. Benjamin Netanyahu called it his plan.
He is obeying someone else's plan.
Okay, who is he obeying?
He is obeying Israel's plan
for the Greater Israel Project,
of which this is one of those things that we can agree on.
Why is he doing that?
I don't know.
Maybe they have something on him.
Maybe they have something on all Americans.
But you think it's a bad thing what he's doing?
Absolutely.
Glad to agree with you.
I don't want to shut down the conversation.
I'm not mocking you, I'm agreeing with you.
Okay, perfect.
But I want to take this opportunity,
because I don't know if I'm going to get the opportunity
again to say, you're not American, first and foremost.
Remember what I said, the agitation from you
is not going to be low.
No, what I'm saying, though.
You came to lower the temperature
and then make racist remarks.
You know that's a racist remark, right?
It's not racist.
You tell an American citizen.
But okay, perfect, perfect.
You just proved your own point.
You just said that was a racist position.
Earlier, you argued this contention
that America has no race,
it's a bunch of immigrants that culminate together.
I never said America has no race.
You inferred it.
You absolutely did.
So now you're saying it's racist
for me to take an American nationalist approach.
What is an American nationalist approach?
Is that a white approach?
I think it's a white nativist approach.
Of course, absolutely.
Only Americans are white people.
Why did your parents immigrate from India?
Americans are white people.
Why did your parents immigrate from India to the UK?
Because the UK colonized and conquered India.
Okay, why did you immigrate to America?
Because, many reasons.
Okay, all opportunity.
There's opportunity. That's not true.
The accent.
Your accent is an afflict of white Anglo-Saxon.
You know there are 50 million Americans
in this country who are immigrants.
I understand, but you're-
None of them are Americans in your view.
What I'm trying to get you to do
to reach a common ground here-
We're not gonna reach a common ground
because you said I'm not American.
Please try.
I don't think you're American.
I'm saying you're not-
I'm saying you're not American due to values.
I don't think you're not American on values either.
I think you're a little fascist-y, a little racist-y.
See, you're using these words.
Okay, first of all, I want to say this.
I'm not just throwing them at you.
You didn't come sit down and I said it.
Every conservative that has ever been shut down
by leftists like you, for every conservative,
for every conservative-
You're not a conservative.
You've already said that.
For every right wing-
You've already said you're not a conservative.
For every Stefan Molyneux, Thomas Sowell, Nick Fuentes,
all of those people-
Is Thomas Sowell American?
He's Australian, but that's not the point.
I'm saying people that are on our side of the aisle
that get shut down by people like you
because you're leveraging this position of emotion.
You're joking, right?
No, I'm not.
You're leveraging a position of emotion.
You know nobody on quote unquote my side of the aisle
is trying to deport you.
Actually, yes, they're trying to.
They're actually trying to genocide my entire race,
so what are you talking about?
Wow.
What are you talking about?
You're a white genocide guy?
Are you kidding me?
You know the fact-
I'm amazed that Jubilee found some of you guys.
How did they find you?
Did they email you?
Do you have Jubilee?
Why are you trying to oust me?
This is such a cheap tactic.
Do you go to Nordstrom?
All immigrants.
Have you ever been on eBay?
No, but I'm a-
You love immigrants.
No, I'm a-
You love immigrants when they're helping you.
You just don't like the color of my skin.
We're having a different conversation.
All right, Thomas.
Pause.
All right, you've been voted out.
Please return to your seat.
Okay.
I really wish we could have asked him.
I mean, you believe in white genocide,
so it's very hard to-